  {
    'Question': 'A Python data type that holds an ordered collection of values, which can be of any type. This is equivalant to an "array" in many other languages. Python <blank>s are "mutable," implying that they can be changed once created.',
    'Answer': 'list',
  },
  {
    'Question': '<blank>s are assigned values using the = operator, which is not to be confused with the == sign used for testing equality. A <blank> can hold almost any type of value such as lists, dictionaries, functions.',
    'Answer': 'variable',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'Python builds <blank>s using the syntax: def <blank>_name(variable): <blank>s can be stand-alone or can return values. <blank>s can also contain other functions.',
    'Answer': 'function',
  },
  {
    'Question': '<blank>s store characters and have many built-in convenience methods that let you modify their content.',
    'Answer': 'string',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'Using <blank> returns the number of _top-level_ items contained in the object being queried. Length of string',
    'Answer': 'len()',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'A function to display the output of a program. Using the parenthesized version is arguably more consistent.',
    'Answer': 'print',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'The <blank> function returns a list of integers, the sequence of which is defined by the arguments passed to it. Used in for loops.',
    'Answer': 'range',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'A <blank> loop permits code to execute repeatedly until a certain condition is met. This is useful if the number of iterations required to complete a task is unknown prior to flow entering the loop.',
    'Answer': 'while',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'Using the <blank> function allows you to represent the content of a variable as a string, provided that the data type of the variable provides a neat way to do so. <blank> does not change the variable in place, it returns a stringified version of it.',
    'Answer': 'str()',
  },
  {
    'Question': 'Name given to the class that is being inherited from',
    'Answer': 'superclass',
  }

